For the people!
- For the people!
Let's go!
Welcome to the Doi Boy Club.
Hey, one martini, please.
- Come here.
- Hey.
The first model is Aui.
He's got a hot body.
This is Lert. I have to say he's gorgeous.
Next one, please.
This is Korn. He's new.
He has been here for less than two months.
He's covered in tattoos.
Okay.
This is Nui. He's still a college student.
He dreams of producing movies.
He's still young.
Are you ready for our special show?
If you are, please give us
a round of applause.
Fuck you.
Do you want to be top or bottom today?
See you later.
Bye.
Som, why are you still up?
The doctor told you to rest a lot.
I was waiting for you.
Why are you home late again?
I don't have enough money for tuition.
I have no money. I have nothing.
BOOZER KARAOKE
Mister, how many of you are here today?
Mister, can I sit with you?
You are a generous man
You give me a garlandevery time you come
May I ask how many garlands
You are giving me today?
Mister, you came so late today
Mister, I got sleepy waiting for you
Do you believe that I haven't got
a single garland today?
I'm starving to death
Because I was waiting for you
BOOZER KARAOKE
WELCOME
See you later, Mister.
Bee, come home with me.
- I can't.
- Bee, come home with me.
Mister, I'll go with you.
Bee is on her period.
It will be a bloody sight.
I'll go with you. Come on.
- See you later.
- Bee.
Let's go.
I thought you were going with him.
Nonsense.
I would have if I wanted to.
I'd rather ride on the back of your bike.
You look much prettier like this.
Don't sweet talk me.
Give me a massage.
Where would you like me to massage you?
Here.
Sorn.
I have something for you.
What is it?
Let me help you with the rent.
Do you have money?
Of course, I just gave you some.
Go lie on the bed.
Do you want to be top or bottom today?
Top.
ASSASSINATION
Let me go.
Sorn.
Yes.
Which shirt should I go with?
This or this?
This one.
Do you believe me?
Of course. Why else would I ask you then?
Why? Did you randomly pick one?
No.
The other one was too revealing,
but it looked nicer.
So the other one it is.
- Is your body ready?
- Yes.
- Is your heart ready?
Is your money ready?
No.
That's too bad
because we are doing it today.
PACKAGE DELIVERY AND MONEY TRANSFER
SERVICE TO SHAN STATE
MONEY EXCHANGE AND TRANSFER
MYANMAR-THAILAND
Take a seat.
Did you bring the required documents?
Birth certificate,
a copy of your employer's
house registration,
and a copy of your employer's
national ID card.
We don't have anything.
Can we still use your service?
Well, it will cost you extra
since you don't have documents.
Normally, you must extend
your work permit every year
and report yourselves
to the immigration department
every three months.
Did you know
any of this?
Not at all?
It's okay.
Come to me for help when the time comes.
I have a question.
Can I go on an airplane
once I have a passport?
Yes, of course.
You must board the plane from Thailand
or go back to Myanmar first.
But it's easier to just cross the border.
How much is it?
It's 20,000 bahts.
Sorn.
Sorn, you are daydreaming again.
Nineteen, twenty.
All 20,000 bahts are here.
Are you doing it too?
It's 20,000 bahts.
- Thank you, Nan.
- You are welcome.
KORWAN CO., LTD.
I'm broke now.
It's fine.
Call Ji, your client.
"Ji, give me some money.
Ji, I need money
to buy a new phone, please."
Fuck you, Korn.
Take this.
I can lift my legs.
How about a race?
Come on.
What are you doing?
Go.
Everyone.
Recently,
the government made an announcement
to close down entertainment venues
for 14 days.
It includes
our Doi Boy Club.
- This sucks.
- What do we do?
- This is unacceptable.
- It's not our fault.
- Other people caused the problem.
- This sucks.
What if my dad needs money?
Aren't they going to help us?
They took a lot of our money.
Where's the help?
- How are we supposed to survive?
- All right, everyone. Be quiet.
Anyway,
I'll do my best to help all of you.
Since today is our last day
before the break,
our club will be packed.
Let's get ready. Come on.
Customers will be here soon.
- We will be jobless.
- Yes.
No.
It's okay. It's on me.
One crispy noodle with gravy sauce to-go
for his wife, please.
Sure.
Hello, Ji.
What brings you here, Joe?
You know why I'm here.
Think about it.
You did a perfect job
last time.
You were untraceable
and impossible to catch.
You know what will happen to you
if you don't take this job, don't you?
I came here to warn you.
I don't want you to end up
like the last guy.
I still want you to go home
to your wife and kid.
Now that you are about to be a dad,
you should think carefully.
Take him to the car.
Let me go.
Let me go, fucker.
Hello, Joe.
I'll take the job.
How's life as a soldier?
Well, it isn't any different
from when I was a monk.
Everybody wakes up,
eats,
and sleeps at the same time.
Chiang Mai is a province
located in the north of Thailand
with an area of approximately
20,107 sq km…
I need all of you to enlist
and fight for our nation.
We are happy as monks.
Don't force them to leave the monkhood.
We either kill them or get killed.
Let me ask you this.
Didn't the Shan people suffer
when Myanmar robbed our food
and burned down our city?
Are you just going to hide in the temple?
What choice do we have?
None.
We don't have a choice.
Why don't we flee to Thailand?
It's very close to here.
But you might
not be able to come back again.
Let's go. Screw this city-saving shit.
It's easier said than done.
You are daydreaming.
I don't mind how things are now.
We have a place to sleep and food to eat.
Do you even know anyone in Thailand?
Have you got your food
and shelter figured out?
No, I have not.
You are inviting me
when you don't have anything figured out.
You don't even have a plan.
I'm not going with you.
Are you really fleeing?
Are you coming with me?
I'll get going then.
Wan.
Are you seriously leaving me here?
I want you to come with me,
but you won't
so I'm choosing what's best for my future.
How did you start working here?
I worked many jobs before this one, Ji.
I used to be a construction worker
and a server.
I saved up money.
My friend named Korn and I
hired a driver
to take us to Chiang Mai.
Boys, wake up. We are here.
Korn.
Come quick.
Come.
Come here.
Get in.
Get in there.
Hurry up.
What for?
Don't ask. Just get in.
Hey, young man.
- Hello.
I haven't seen you in Thailand
for a while.
What goods are you delivering today?
Groceries, as usual.
- Can I take a look?
- Go ahead.
I was informed by word of mouth
that this job paid well
so I decided to give it a try.
- Hello.
Hi, are you here to apply for a job?
- Yes.
- What's your name?
I'm Korn.
I'm Wan.
Wan?
Wan again?
His name is Wan.
His name is also Wan.
A few more of you
and I'll have a whole week.
I'll give you a new name.
Sorn.
From now on, you are Sorn.
Repeat after me, Sorn.
- Sorn.
- Yes.
Since today is your first day, work hard.
You are new to Chiang Mai, aren't you?
Yes.
- How do you know?
- Those green shoes gave it away.
Every soldier who flees the army
has those shoes.
Since it's your first day, work hard.
Kindly ask your customers for tips.
Work hard.
- All right?
- Thank you.
Handsome.
The job felt weird at first,
but I got used to it after a while.
Guess what I bought
after I got my first check.
A motorbike?
No.
A phone?
It was a pair of shoes.
Why?
My friends here teased me
about my old shoes.
Really?
Yes.
I have to blend in with Thai people
as much as I can.
When the police see foreigners
with those shoes
and who look out of place,
they often ask to see ID.
I'm terrified of the police.
They always extort money.
Policemen are dicks.
The truth is I sneaked in quietly.
I picked the lock.
REVENGE
NEEWAK
STOP ENFORCED DISAPPEARANCE
What did he do?
He was a bad man.
He caused social conflict and disharmony.
Stop hurting the people!
He kept blaming the government.
It's tear gas! Run!
Nothing would have happened
if he had kept to his duty as a student.
Tyrant bootlickers!
Our country needed peace.
- Fuck you!
- Your salary is our tax payment!
Ji.
Can I go with you after our session ends?
You are usually in a rush to go home.
I only have 400 bahts left on me.
The club will close from tomorrow.
I don't know what I'm going to do.
Sure.
Come with me tonight.
Let's find something exciting to do.
Thank you.
NO ONE SHALL BE SUBJECTED
TO ENFORCED DISAPPEARANCE
Do you see the guy putting up the posters?
His name is Wuth.
He's 22 years old.
On the outside,
he looks like an ordinary boy.
He was probably out drinking.
He's my next target.
Would you be interested
in a job?
I would.
What kind of job is it?
A guide.
Show me and my friend around
your hometown in Myanmar.
How will you get there?
Isn't the border closed due to COVID-19?
The same way you entered Thailand.
But
it's very dangerous.
I don't want to go back to my country now.
Are you going to show us
around your hometown or not?
No, sorry.
BOOZER KARAOKE
Hey, Sorn.
- See you later.
- See you.
No man is trying to take you home tonight.
There weren't any customers.
I didn't get any tips.
It's okay. Things will be better tomorrow.
The bar will be closed from tomorrow.
It's not the end of the world.
Let's go home.
Come on. Give me a smile.
Sorn.
Have you paid the rent?
I asked, have you paid the rent?
No.
Where's the money I gave you?
What did you do with it?
I used it to get a passport.
How are we going to live?
I thought I would be able
to make more money if I had a passport
so I borrowed your money.
Where's your passport then?
Where's the money?
Things are slow during the pandemic.
The club is closed.
Then why did you spend the money?
What was I supposed to do?
Why didn't you ask me first?
Hello, Nan.
- Hello.
Wash your hands first.
You are not wearing a mask.
We want to know
the status of our passports.
The process started only a few days ago.
They aren't ready yet. Be patient.
Can we have our money back?
I'm sorry, but it's too late for a refund.
Do you know
when our passports will be ready?
Listen, I'm waiting
for your passports too.
But you know how the pandemic
is slowing everything down.
But the passports aren't here yet.
What are you doing with our money?
I didn't force you to give me the money.
You walked in here yourselves.
Do you remember?
I remember.
But I need the money.
Can you give me back the money?
Help me out, please.
I'm doing the best I can.
Don't you understand
that it's the pandemic?
- We should go.
- I understand.
- Yes, go home.
- Let's go, Sorn.
I'll call you
when the passports are ready.
Don't ask me again.
I have no choice
since I've run out of money.
He talks like we are rich or something.
The pandemic
is taking a toll on all of us.
I need two carpenters
and two concrete finishers.
You can go.
It didn't use to be this hot
when we first got here.
We wouldn't have decided
to work at the club if we hadn't thought
labor work was hot and tiring.
Yes, you are right.
I need five workers.
Hey.
What type of job
do you think he has for us?
Whatever it is, just do it.
The police are here.
Go.
Sorn!
May I see your work permit?
What documents do you have?
Do you have a passport?
If you don't have any documents,
we will have to lock you up.
But my passport is arriving soon.
I have a number you can call.
No.
Can I talk to your boss then?
Are you trying to get on my nerves?
Hey, lock him up.
He's pissing me off.
Please calm down, Lieutenant.
I'll take care of him.
All right.
Ji.
Are you a cop?
What happened to you?
What brought you here today?
I was arrested for having no passport.
Really? Hasn't Nan given you the passport?
Do you know Nan?
Do you remember the job I offered you?
What do you think now?
Have you changed your mind?
What are you talking about?
I want you to be my guide
and take me and my friend to your hometown
in Myanmar.
I don't know why
you don't want to go back home.
But if you don't want to go to jail,
you will have to help me.
Will I be able to come back to Thailand
if I cross the border?
This is just a partial payment.
Once you finish the job,
I will pay you money too.
But you have to promise me first
that you will help me.
I've checked the VPN. It's secured.
They won't be able to trace us.
Bitch, I know it's dangerous,
but I have to retrieve the hard disk.
I'll recheck everything again
before I leak it tomorrow.
Have you prepared
an escape route for me?
They aren't joking around this time.
See you soon.
Bye.
I have a gun. Don't make a noise.
Don't resist. Just follow me.
Calm down, boy. Calm down.
You are Wuth, right?
Why are you so concerned
about human trafficking?
Why are you risking your life over it?
Do you know who you are messing with?
I have every reason to.
Put yourself in my shoes.
You would do the same thing as me
if you were in my position.
Have you thought of it that way?
Do you really think
you can change the system?
It's better than doing nothing.
Honestly,
I wouldn't be sitting here
if Bhoom was still alive.
Is it worth it?
I might kill you today.
Do you think it will be over?
When I go missing,
someone else will come out
and fight for me.
Just like how I'm fighting for Bhoom.
I'm wondering
if it was your parents, your kid,
or your wife
sitting here, not me,
would you treat them
the way you are treating me now?
You murderer.
Breakfast is ready, Bhoom.
Eat your breakfast first.
Wuth, look at this.
Eaun sent this to me.
The documents say
that high-ranking officials and executives
are involved in human trafficking.
What's your plan?
I'm going to expose them.
I'll be right back.
Bhoom.
Why don't you eat first?
I'll be back to eat soon.
See you later.
What are you going to do next?
We just have to get Wuth ordained
at the temple you ordained at.
And everything will be over.
Are you going to kill him?
I'm supposed to get rid of Wuth
like I did Bhoom.
But I'm not going to kill him.
I've committed enough sin.
Why did you do it the first time then?
Back then, I had no choice.
But I have a choice now.
Because I have you.
What about me? Do I have a choice?
What's wrong?
A checkpoint. There's a checkpoint ahead.
Stay here. I'll take care of it.
Please untie me.
Let's run away together.
Let's run away, Sorn.
STOP THE CAR
Let them pass.
I need a backup!
Let's split up.
Hey, where are you going?
I can't trust you.
But thank you.
Don't run away again.
You will be home soon, Sorn.
Are you happy?
I don't want to go home.
We will arrive soon, Wuth.
Shut the fuck up.
I heard everything.
You killed Bhoom.
You are a murderer.
I'm supposed to kill you too.
You know that, right?
I'm risking my life to save yours.
You will be dead
if I don't bring you across the border.
And it won't just be you.
Your parents, siblings, and friends
will die too.
I'm helping you right now.
You aren't doing shit.
It doesn't matter if I die or not,
but people shouldn't be erased
for trying to say the truth.
How far?
It's a short walk from here.
Can I take a break?
What?
Sure. Sorn, let's take a break here.
It'll be easier to walk around.
Who are you? Hands up.
Ji, Wuth, put your hands up.
Yoon?
Wan?
Tie them up.
- Come here.
- Come.
You are Wan, aren't you?
Why the fuck did you come back?
Why?
Is it so bad to be a soldier?
Is it?
Say something.
You, son of a bitch.
You, coward.
You ran away,
leaving your family
to fight for your nation.
We've never won against Myanmar
because of people like you.
Everyone, lock him up in prison.
Yes, sir.
Yoon.
I'm your friend.
Yoon, are you going to leave me here?
Why the fuck
did you come back then, idiot?
You don't want to kill me.
You want me to survive.
You want to torture me
by making me live in hiding.
So you can feel better about yourself
for not killing me.
But it's too late to right your wrongs.
You've killed someone.
He's not coming back.
Just follow your boss's order.
Finish me off.
Don't you realize at all
that I brought you all the way here
and I'm sparing your life
because I want to quit?
You want to quit?
Do you see now
how fucked up the system is?
Fucker, soon enough,
the system will collapse
and crush everyone under it,
including yourself.
Someone's coming. Hide.
Stay here.
What are they trying to do?
I told them to go back to Thailand.
Why are they still here?
They don't want to return to Thailand.
They came here to take
that man to the temple.
I see.
Let's take a break.
What's the plan?
Ji, what's the plan?
I'm leaving Wuth with you.
You have to take Wuth to the temple.
As for me,
I have to return to Thailand.
If they can't contact me
when the sun rises,
we will all be in trouble.
If I bring you back to Thailand,
I will have to kill you.
I have no choice.
Please stay here.
It's for your own good.
All your belongings are in this bag.
Wan.
Can you do me a favor?
What is it?
Can you tell him to shoot me
in the shoulder?
Ji, he asks you
to shoot him in the shoulder.
Let's use my gun.
It will be more believable.
Cover your ears.
Are we almost there yet?
Just keep walking.
We'll get there eventually.
What does that mean?
It means stop complaining
and keep walking.
Hurry up.
Come on.
Come on, let's take a swim.
Just strip naked.
Come on.
Wait a second.
It's cold.
Stop.
Hey.
I wonder if I'll miss home.
I might miss Thailand like crazy.
I thought you hated Thailand.
How can I hate my home country?
I love my home country.
I want to make it better.
I want to live a good life
with the person I love.
I don't even know where to call home.
It's okay.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Do I have to hold it tightly?
- Okay.
- Next, you twist it with your right hand.
- Next…
Like this?
Hold it. Pull it tight.
- Twist it like this?
- Yes.
I have to hold it high.
- Not too high.
- Okay.
- Like this?
- Yes.
- After that…
- I take my arm out like this, right?
- Yes.
- Now what?
Then place it on your shoulder.
Don't I look pretty, Mrs. Sorn?
My mind might run even wilder here.
You'll get used to it soon.
Think of this temple
as another home of yours.
Yes.
I guess I'll do that.
This is yours.
Ji left it for you.
Use it to return to Thailand.
Bee, why the long face?
Have you not found Sorn yet?
No.
Why don't you report him missing?
There's no point
reporting a missing alien.
Nobody will give a darn.
They will extort him for money.
He doesn't have any documents.
Poor guy.
I feel sorry for him.
Stay with Daddy Meng for the time being.
I heard he's a sugar daddy.
Hey.
He's offering to give you so many things,
a condo and a car.
Just accept them.
Don't think about it too much.
The pandemic isn't over yet.
Use those assets to start a life
with your boyfriend.
This bitch.
Put a smile on your face.
You are paid to be here.
Here I come.
- Where were you?
- I'm here. That's enough.
You are late to the party.
After this glass, someone's taking a dip.
- Hello.
- How much?
- It's 1,500 bahts.
Come on, the economy is bad.
How about 1,200 bahts?
I will pay 1,000 bahts.
Deal.
What will you do for 1,000 bahts?
It's up to you. I'll do anything.
Get in.
It's hard being poor.
Not really.
Whatever, Mr. Billionaire.
What does a luxurious life sound like?
Well…
Once I win the lottery,
we will run away together,
stay in a fancy hotel, and stuff ourselves
to death with seafood.
How does that sound?
How much are you paying me?
Som.
Inspector.
Have you heard from Ji?
No.
But I've sent every man looking for him.
You didn't need to come all the way here.
It could be you!
- It could be you!
No one should be forced…
- To go missing!
It could be you!
- It could be you!
No one should be forced…
- To go missing!
It could be you!
- It could be you!
No one
should be forced
to go missing.
It could be you!
…should be forced to go missing.
Subtitle translation by:
Pet-chompoo Sa-ngarmangkang