Here they come.
Let's go now boys.
I'm fucking kids.
Don't bother it, I'm Patrick.
Oh, that's all we need.
That's it!
I'm just leaving!
Fuckin' move it!
You're a Demi-as-out-shout-fen-bar.
You over there?
I can see what you're up to, right?
How can I bloody blast them
if I can't freakin' see them?
Move them back up to
the top of the roof there.
The wind, I can't hear.
All right, sure.
If you're implying that I'm
cheating, guard O'Shea.
I'll take it very thick.
Well, there's a wager. It has to be fair.
Are you gonna winch about fairness all day?
Or are you gonna take your shot and lose?
Like you always do.
Hope you're whole.
Come on with ya.
Seat for a little bastard.
Thank you.
Robin, me blind, you whore.
So what is the day, promise?
Apart from feeding
your cat and pondering
human reason with
Gulliver and the little folk?
I've finished Gulliver's troubles.
I'm on to Mr. Dostoyevsky now.
Rush some rider.
He is the no-nothing of him.
I think Christie's gonna make a cup of tea.
Where are we going?
No, I'm a bit of a visual business.
Mrs. Bailey come up to
me and said the welcome
saying to the town this
way has gone missed.
No, you'll see what real work entails.
God, that's the best of a mess.
Maroon.
Burgundy.
It's not a bad car back.
The agent must have
lost control of the car.
Or drunk.
Hi.
Probably thick in the head.
See, you'll be looking for
some metal case in town now.
Hi.
Shouldn't need them but tea time, so...
I can feel your eyes
on the back of my head.
Read up.
I have no doubt.
Adam would have traded his Eve for you.
Have you saw this place?
Well, it's best to have a Holly.
Oh, a little bright in a bomb.
With a table of seven.
Would you would know if you'd ever
accepted my invitation to dinner? I saw.
I was Brandon holding up.
He's far too worse to be getting better.
So would the Feignon woman like herself?
There's one he won't be hanging around.
Loaden left six dead,
including three children.
The IRA is believed to
be behind the bombing,
though they have yet
to claim responsibility.
Anyone with information about the
attack is encouraged to come forward.
Alright, waiting down.
I can't see enough
without this next person.
It's done more for this
town than we deserve.
A man of many talents, in fact,
with a little encouragement
perhaps he'd treat us here tonight.
Bart McGinnis.
Would you honor us
with a song? Oh, no.
You can't talk.
What do you know? Let me see.
Give me your attention.
Can we have enough?
I wish I was in Carrick Fergus.
Only for nights in Ballygran.
I would swim off her.
The deepest ocean.
You're not just shooting me here.
This day I was both this exercise.
Keep water right on the left.
Here I'll be fine.
Two steps to your right.
Start digging.
Where are we?
We're going to spend eternity here.
Nice to know what I am.
Donnie Gore.
You're in Donnie Gore, the
other round of the country.
The Forgotten County seems fitting.
And this is how you earn a living.
She's deep enough.
How'd you get? On your knees.
Jesus.
On these trees.
You've been busy? On your knees.
Now it's behind the old head there.
You have one minute.
Say what you will.
Play it if you want.
Makes no odds.
No pleading necessary.
I knew this day was coming.
Mind you, it took longer than I thought.
It was a lifetime ago.
But a fierce temper is a lad.
Did my share a killing?
I knew that there was no
going back to what I'd done.
But one day I decided that
whatever was left of my withering soul.
shouldn't be wasted, so.
Somehow I blew that black cloud away.
Became part of the community.
Did what I could for those around me.
You know, this is where it ends.
For people like us.
In some windswept bucket patch.
Train to some good before
you find yourself here.
If only so much time.
Ah, but my days are numbered.
Come all you young men and lay me down.
Many a deer has to fall.
So are the hiccups and kev.
You're queer, Robert.
Your music suggests you're queer.
You slow kev.
Your boots suggest you're slow.
Got a magic muck in the
mess you left out there.
That's a brilliant moody blues, 45.
I'm gonna borrow this one.
And dojans draws the
weak to an early grave.
Who's that? Yeah, it's.
..
It's my mother.
Who's that?
Only me and Mrs. McKee.
Oh, the mower, are you?
Robbie said you were coming in.
So I'd made your favorite scones for you.
Oh, Terry, huh? Reason.
I thought it was raised.
I couldn't stop.
Well, it is.
You know me better than I know myself.
I thought so.
You'll take them with you then.
I will.
You've never not taken them.
Ah, good food and mornin' ya, buttes.
That was hot.
Hey, hey, hey, manners.
There it is.
The fastest hand in the West.
No, that was a Dublin mile.
Kiss and kiss.
Oh, God.
Here we are.
Oh, yourself.
Hey.
Oh, you auditioned.
Mm-hmm.
It took it as payment
from the O'Reilly clan.
Some Mexican fella painted it.
Quite en vogue in America, apparently.
Worth a lot more than I was old.
Too bad you can't sell a
back to us right from home.
Oh, uh, he than I had.
I'd have something else
for you in a week or so.
Yeah, it's the end.
Good job.
Give it to him.
All of them.
Been thinking quite a bit lately.
Been a lifetime of pure choices of me and
Robert Jefferson's Margaret died, you know.
I mean, there's more to me than this.
I'd like folks to see it.
Oh, and, uh, what is it you're
so anxious to show the world?
This is all you know.
I could plant a garden.
A garden.
All right.
So, you're just going to jail me?
Well, leave me with that gone bean.
You're going to miss me.
Like an old man.
What seeds do you
want? I have seeds.
They're not ones for buying seeds, so do I.
No, not before.
Are you sure about seeds?
At least, have you
caught any or not? All right.
We have, uh,
Broad beans, cabbage, some of carrots,
and there's really
other stuff there to eat.
So, I was thinking I could
start a garden in my own.
A bit of popple.
Maybe some goldenrod.
Like that yellow wave
you've got going out there.
Goldenrod is a weed, Finbar.
Didn't know that.
Might need a teacher, so.
Is it okay?
I don't know what I'm enjoying more.
The food or the company.
Was your way for good cook?
Margaret, was it?
Often where I'm sorry.
I didn't.
No, no, no.
You're fine.
It's just been so long since
I've heard her name spoken.
Margaret.
Oh, she's experimenting.
She baked this break.
It's just a long time ago.
Put apples and nuts into the mix.
We bit a cinnamon thrown in there.
Never tasted the leg of it.
Oh, it's not gorgeous.
Jesus, no, it was awful.
It's like I said.
I never tasted the leg of it.
And thankfully, I never did again.
Was this in Dublin?
Hi.
Sure.
Past the bookshop where
she worked every day.
Welcome to the factory, you know.
God, she loved those books.
It got me hooked.
I wish it could have mattered.
Well, it was too good for me now, woman.
It's him as yourself.
I'll just be with none.
Hmm.
How's it going?
If you hook a rod, be
careful because that line
could cut into the palm
of your hand, darling.
Here.
Come on, use that.
There you go.
Good girl.
What are you hoping
to catch? The goldfish.
Take him home.
Call him Goldie.
A fish wouldn't care for you.
And my dad, Daddy, is
to say that you shouldn't
care for those that
don't care for you.
It didn't fair enough.
I was told to get a fish for dinner.
You're on.
That's some lay note.
Oh, yeah.
It's okay.
Where did you snare? Finnbar.
It's price to see you in person like this.
Kevin.
Finnbar.
He's grumpy tonight.
Oh, they'll bastard.
Never in your life.
Hi.
And this is my one night out.
I've made a plane for
the grumpy bollocks who
need a baby sound for
his long suffering wife.
I have a wee black bush, please.
Flash in the cache.
I've driven books ever and
you're living on every note.
As long as I keep winning
money of you, I'll do you just think.
Any luck cuts in your evil, Knievel boy?
Ah, not a bit of it.
Now, it hasn't been most food
for the days, I have to admit.
But I'll get him.
I'm sure you are.
Hey, what's up, please?
I'm in Finland there, son.
Thank you, my friend.
That's an old tune.
Old as the hills, but
it always has a place.
You stay that here?
Old as the hills?
We call it a jig.
Of course.
Thank you.
So what brought you over here?
Long ago, an Irish
man came to my village,
playing the most beautiful
song I'd ever heard.
He left before I could lend
it, so I just had to come.
Do you not miss it?
No.
I do not miss the fighters.
I do not miss the broad.
So you're loyal, but the
bridge is efficient for dinner.
Sounds like my way and all right.
She's our own woman.
We're like ships passing in the night.
We're working here all
the hours, good sense.
Don't be giving her too much grief.
What's that?
The box I grew up, but
tumbled into the river.
What?
That was not me.
I was the apanant distract in her.
Great.
Well, thanks for the hands up.
Let's be the answers.
I'll talk to you soon.
Where are you after?
Surely you're not fleeing
over the spilled food.
Oh, yeah.
That told you her marvellous
one, what are you doing?
She's going to miss you something shocking.
Stuck out here alone.
and you off right in the plains.
You're brave and loyal.
I've seen those horses hit the dark.
Scared stuff of the rabbit
holes and the rabbits.
Best to run away during the day.
So you don't, you know, run
into anything when I expect it.
What's up to you, I
suppose, the other boss.
Do, do, do.
You're now still on the caravan.
Hi, my mom says we're
gonna go and never be done.
You can go now.
What? You can go now.
No, no, a gentleman always
leaves the lady to the door.
I said I'm fine.
What the fuck?
Where's he been?
The fucking star in here.
Who's this? A gentleman.
Oh.
It's just like your real uncle Curtis said.
You're not my uncle.
Here you watch her back talk.
Do you hear me?
Women, eh?
Fuckin' nightmares.
Oh, if that isn't a wonder,
I'll buy it from Mr. Traveler.
I can straight away, just when we get in.
What the fuck is this?
Apples?
I don't know if this is how to get in here.
You've been gone for two hours
and you come back to be apples.
Is there something fucking wrong with you?
Hey!
What the fuck up?
What the fuck is this easy to her brother?
He's don't even sound the same.
He's don't even business.
What are you doing all this time?
I've just been waiting down to Caravan.
I don't even need to be
hanging around down there.
You just get what we
need and you come back.
Don't you understand?
Where's Mark? Oh, Jesus.
I mean, thank you.
Why is this heavy?
Will you take a cup of tea?
No, no, thanks, girl.
Is Mark up?
What have you got there?
Not got anything.
Maybe I said I was your mother.
No, please.
Don't say anything to her.
Show me.
Come on, show me.
Put it togethers.
Did your uncle give you this?
He's not my uncle.
Why did he give this to you, man?
There's a good something to do with these.
These bruises on you.
Oh, yeah.
Let something happen.
You don't want me to tell me about it.
You're a blast.
So the gentleman caller returns.
Morning, Sinead.
Morning, my eh.
Hope you're not thinking about
making a move in our Sinead.
She's a wee bit young for you, I'd say.
Shut your hole, Curtis.
Do you mind him for him, Barry?
He's an arsehole.
Well, I can't even have a
wee bit of chitchat with locals.
Me and him are sweet.
And they're out there, man.
Ah, here we go.
Nothing like a wee bit of skinny
div in the work of an appetite.
Just take it and go.
I'll bring you more tonight after work.
I'm going off my fucking number.
Can't blame me for wanting
a wee bit of a new company.
Fuck you.
Catch you later, Princess.
Old friend.
You can pick your friends.
You don't get to choose
your bloody and lost.
I, um...
My brother married his sister.
And promptly got himself killed.
I can't wait to see the back of him.
I thought you were all for
leaving this business behind.
Give it to that wee bollocks, Kevin.
I'd pay.
Are you wise?
A local fella?
You want the boys and blue at your door?
This clan isn't from here.
He's a blue one.
But the name of
Curtis... I don't care.
Not on our doorstep.
Besides, it could be IRA.
Now, look, stay in the way from
them fellows to the rest of your life.
So, we just let him keep on hurting her.
You don't even know what he's done.
I know.
I could see it in her eyes.
And that's his message
for her to keep quiet.
Jesus, he's a child, Robert.
Shop him to the guards.
An anonymous tip off.
Mm, consciously.
You'll never tell him what he's done.
He's put the fear of God on her.
And he'll never stop.
He'll just go on to men and others.
Robert, I know what I said about killing.
But this is different.
I want no part of it, Finbar.
Count me out.
Taking your bros for a walk.
So, you actually can't talk, huh?
Only when I'm done listening.
Have some bice and eads hop in.
I'll give you a lift.
Bye.
So, you're an holiday,
eh? Aye, holiday.
Fuck up.
Putting it off in New York, it
fixed my farmer's time, but nah.
That's all squat in the bag, ours
are bleeding fucking nowhere.
Listen, there's cigarettes
in the front there, help or so.
The matches are on the floor.
The funny road never looks
the same on the way back.
That's because giants made these hills.
Aye, is that right?
This land was once ruled by famoreans.
God like seafarers, they were.
Slaved the land at the
children, so the story goes.
Now, to think I just
used them for shooting.
You're under?
Well, if you call shooting bean
cans in the old Jack Rabbit hunt,
then yes, I'm a stupendous hunter.
What do you use? A Smith door.
He hates fucks.
Teddy Roosevelt called it
the finest gun never made.
Whoo.
You wanna see it?
I had a Remington 17 model
before I got this little baby.
Wasn't as nifty.
Didn't have the same.
Bossy qualities.
Beautiful, isn't he?
You want a holder?
We Moya, you bastard.
She's fucking right.
I'll leave.
You'll never fucking see me again.
You're fucking dead.
You're poverty.
So ginger, Jesse Owens, he was.
We did have a knife.
Is that something only young men's carry?
Wouldn't consider me self-intune
what modern you to be fair.
What are you doing out here?
Robert asked me to check up on you.
I did, Teddy.
Yeah.
Well, I'm not a kiss.
I like bingo.
Royce has a session on tonight.
You'll pay for me books.
That cheeky point that too, well.
Oh, what the hell are you
and almost? I'll get down.
Get down.
Christ.
I don't understand why they range so much.
This Yahoo one time.
Taking away so he was.
What he knew?
That when he stopped, I was there.
Yeah?
End of the line.
So he just didn't stop.
What should be something like
nine feet when he was done with it?
Oh, please, there's the size of plumes.
Who knows?
He could have taken Fiji or someplace.
I just stood in love.
There was something else.
It's all a big joke to you, isn't it?
That's a line of work.
Oh, well.
As my dad always used to say.
Do a job, you love.
And the next one up is stuck in a tree, 53.
Can you go, Fender?
I'm here for yesterday.
I forgot sex.
Yeah, there's no need.
Yeah, love.
My one.
My two-inch part, Kevin.
She's a foisty one.
Wines me on her left in
the forest no longer, though.
For more 34.
A woman? Yeah.
I'm collected in the
fellas, don't you think?
Mark Dignity before a dime.
You never?
No.
There's enough cruel man in this world.
She was cruel, already.
For real and looking.
66.
I would be crying to the edge of her.
We've been messed up
in the head, aren't you?
This is the one.
It's just a bit of money in
me pocket when I need it.
But a body can't look like yours.
Now that's like cutting.
You listen to me, shit.
Killing has no juke and matter to me.
And I'm done with it for good.
But if I ever hear of you having a
laugh at someone else's day in tears,
I'll beat you with my own long hands.
You know, many people,
have you killed a lot together?
Who runs my thing off in there?
You know, the day they murdered her father,
Curtis has played
football in the under-twins.
Little bollocks wasn't half bad.
I never forget picking him
up, telling him what happened.
He just sat there, just looking at me.
He couldn't make sense of it.
Him growing up bad first
to me, down south to a man.
His whole world turned upside down.
And I made him a promise.
I said I'd always look out for him.
Conan says we should clear it.
And it tracks the fronts somewhere.
How about my brother?
He probably just had a lock and...
drinking, you know what he's like.
And as he developed
the power of invisibility,
a course he didn't spend
the night in a fucking lock-in.
Think a fucking pig?
We're not going anywhere without Curtis.
He's fucking left, is there?
He's probably away on home.
No, he's dead if he goes back. We all are.
Yeah, I know.
Curtis, June, and Duren,
you're the reason we're in this mess.
I knew you would fuck it up.
But we got the bastards, didn't we?
That's what matters.
And what about the kids?
What would they just clatter?
You know fucking rightly, I
couldn't have predicted that.
You made yourself known.
Me and Sheamus, we were in the clear.
They only saw the back of
her head running on a road.
I saw the back of her head last night.
Fuck!
The morning he's in the tensions.
Where are you going?
I'm going out to find the sad bastard,
whose only job was to lay low.
Of course he's doing
that only too fucking well.
If you can't swim and leave that's grand.
Just don't be expected big fucking hogs
when you get back to Belfast.
Curtis! Hey, Sister.
What are you doing out of the bungalow?
Yesterday, did Curtis say
where he was heading?
I didn't say me yesterday.
That's always messing.
I should never have
let you back in my life.
Go on, pack your shit, I want you's gone.
Don't you dare speak to me like that.
I'll fucking rip that
tongue from your throat.
Maybe the payer's got him.
They're probably closing in the
rest of you sorry fucking bastards.
I'm fighting for a free Ireland.
And that includes you.
You cunt.
So you better start showing
me some fucking respect.
What did he tell you?
He said nothing.
I'm not stupid Darren.
I read the payer's.
I'm okay.
Here, you swam most days.
Maybe you're fucking drowned.
Jesus, here we're going
to let your age get to you.
I suppose the front line would
make a decent shout out of anyone.
Now where's Curtis?
Ah, tonight's a bit the last of your life.
You know, I never knew
the hell of war that you did.
For me, the liberation
of France was just a
load of faffing about,
from perfectly honest.
But the monkey as well, you can bite.
Well, they certainly weren't up to me.
They feel good about it.
They was determined to help
fight through Nazi bastards,
even if it meant sided with the English.
But that's why I wear the uniform.
You know, I know right, I know wrong.
And you need the black and white.
Oh, the state of the North at the minute.
And I've seen that off
fighting for a lifetime.
Hey! There you go.
Did anyone come out here? Does anyone know?
So he could be back in Belfast then.
At the end, they'd fucking
kick him back to him himself.
What if special branches aren't us?
I fuck off!
Just give me something!
Local intel, any names,
round here, someone of no!
Where are you again?
Dang, Glenn, call him.
Let's just suppose.
Based hiding spots, it was
against fucking pronouns.
Yeah, yeah.
No, stay back.
Robert, my cue? No, I'm not.
Before is that happened?
Your, uh, colleague.
What's the specific about
the nature of your visit?
Afraid his phone was being tapped
by the big fellas, I suppose, huh?
Oh, bloody paranoid.
Trying to find a friend.
And none know what the shadow is
better than those under their rocks.
Oh, I like that.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
And this friend, what's
the name? Curtis.
Curtis June.
That's a foliar name,
huh? And the June.
Hi.
June.
Is it short for something?
What is June?
Is June fucking short for something?
It's June, like the month.
June.
I've never in my life
been anyone called June.
Redhead, tall, skinny fella.
That doesn't ring a bell.
You know, those bandits out there in the
west, they might have heard something.
You give them a try.
You know, I have to clear up this mess.
If you please, find your own way out.
My fits.
I said... I heard you.
You're only three foot away from me.
Is he dead?
Without a doubt.
I have nothing to do with me.
Who, then?
Ten-year-old blow your fucking head off.
Well, well, well, put it away, will you?
I'm not sticking my life for him.
Told him not to do it.
Who? Finn Maher.
Finn Maher, Murphy.
But we parted ways.
He's no longer in my employ.
Who called the his?
We'd have to ask him that.
Where does he
live? I don't know.
Now, if you don't mind, I would be
very grateful if you would get that out.
Robbie?
Robbie's not here anymore.
Where is he? I shot him.
Believe me, he had a comment.
I'm not trying to be
disrespectful or nothing.
What's your name, love?
Josie?
You're a sweet voice, Josie.
I'm sure you've done nothing wrong.
But I can't let you go
see in my face now, can I?
No.
So why don't you go into your
bedroom back there, lock your door,
and don't come out until I'm gone?
Robbie isn't going anywhere.
Put that away.
Take a look at this.
Blood money.
Fuck him, last I go.
Thanks again, Rita.
Oh, wait a minute.
I'll teach a bit whenever you start
planting, but I can't remember everything.
Looks have done good.
That's a start.
Good night.
Night.
Robbie.
No, no, no.
Mr. McKade, don't.
Robbie was a good man.
Of course he fook him, wasn't he?
Why?
For what he was, he was a good man.
Did you think who
he was? It was her.
No, I didn't.
She was talking to Robbie, though.
She said she was looking
for someone named Curtis.
The ginger Jesse.
She'll need a show.
We can't stay here.
Good.
Fucking hate whites.
Going safe in some of the bedroom.
Let's make you go into the kitchen.
Please.
All right.
I'll start this out.
Everyone knows each
other in these small towns.
They'll know them.
But why does it have to be me?
Because you always look lost.
Now go.
Good evening.
I'm up for the weekend.
As of my uncle.
We've got a bit turned around.
You wouldn't happen to
know a Finn Bar Murphy.
Finn Bar?
No, I'm all right.
Object the road there.
Mother fucks you.
Gosh.
Thank you.
Evening, Garda.
The event.
You want me to follow
her up? Huh? Yeah.
Never see that fellow around here before.
Never have.
this is up to see us,
Uncle Finn, by? Fiber.
But, uh, no, Don's never
said he had enough of you.
I suppose they found them.
Maybe you asked this
network a bit to skirt us, fella.
Chet on the road after you spoke to them.
Just wait for your outside, then.
How long you been?
I've been over there.
Something spooky.
Somebody's in my house.
Well, that's me and
employed, then I suppose.
Old Robert took advantage
of me, but he treated me right.
You say you was my friend?
We had things in common.
Things to keep hidden.
But you're a runaway.
Your home is an old pilot shooting.
There's no luck to be had out here.
They call it running away.
Escaping's more like you.
One night, I got myself
into a fierce post-op in a pub.
But I come out of it on top.
And there Robert was.
Buying me as many points as I wanted,
an after-me-tirty quest to
push some fella off up here.
Of course I didn't know he was getting 130,
but that was Robert the
elf's sleeve and bastard.
It was easy, money.
And I lost track long ago.
And many have killed.
The war had turned me into
somebody that didn't recognize.
And when I came home and
learned my market had died,
but it was left to my old self.
It seemed to disappear into a black hole.
And then Robert came home.
As he said, it was too easy.
Fuckin' seniors and their raisins.
But he's not here by now.
He's probably like down watching us.
Well, if he is, let's give
him something to watch.
No, it's easier.
Go back inside, Rita.
Please.
You must be the nosy fucking neighbor, huh?
You should be minding your own
business if you know what's best.
You know, Fimper?
Never had the pleasure, but I will.
Mr. Murphy has done something.
Something unforgivable.
Hey, what is it?
I'm gonna fucking kill her.
You've got no advantage.
I found it. What's that
water talk? Put it down.
I don't want Rita getting
caught in my crossfire.
God, it's lonely out here.
Especially for a frail
owl one, like yourself.
If you see your friend, you
can give him a message.
I'll tell him a mighty wee bitch, Santa.
Do.
Talk to the crew.
Hold it! Phew.
Do you cut this is down
from the crossroads?
One of the flowers.
And who is this again?
For God's sake, it doesn't matter.
Look, you're a doctor. Just go to her.
All right? Please.
Here we are.
Home sweet home.
Huh.
This money's worth here.
No wonder you need someone
to buy your bingo boots.
Maybe I just went to the conversation.
Did you play this thing?
Just a card, I too.
No trainer, I want you to teach me stuff.
I'll make my own rack out someday.
Maybe over there in California, if
we can save enough for the journey.
People over there just
seem free or something.
Enjoying life, you know what I mean?
The teams, that's...
Oh, hey, let's go.
There's Dr. Ocogli, you've
earned the paper before.
I don't recall you being sober.
Hey, what?
Hey.
It was 20-year-old yesterday.
Feenborough.
The poor fellow must have been a hermit
out there, for I never saw him in the town.
Went to the name of Robert McHugh.
Did you know him at all? Mm-hmm.
The mother said that there
was a woman that did the killing.
I can't make a head
in her tail a bit at all.
You know, I was wondering if maybe
the same had something to do with it.
You know, maybe the same was the same.
Anyway, we'll get the
detectives down from Dublin.
There'll be all over it.
There'll be nothing for me to do.
Oh, here.
You never told me you had an FU.
Oh, nice lad.
I don't see him that much.
You mind dropping me
by some notes? Oh, get in.
Well.
..
It's yours for the ride, Vinny.
Yeah, hey.
Don't be smug about it.
Can't be seem to have favorites.
Get on with it.
Stay.
No.
Stay out of sight.
You come to a fucking football match.
He'd be here.
Ruts.
We're gonna wear fucking ruts.
They didn't get your good side.
This pushes us in the corner.
We're gonna have to leg it.
Not yet.
Anybody can recognize a storm.
Curtis is dead.
Try to give in ounces, shit.
Let's burn the fucker's
place to go around for Curtis.
Let me get out of here.
We'll get the Amsterdam France.
Maybe we've got that
money we can start over.
Have you lost your fucking mind?
Run off and leave Ireland.
So what's the point of all this day?
If we want to live.
So they died for nothing.
For a while, nothing's settled down.
Am I the only one who understands
what we're fighting for here?
We're not fucking leaving.
Someone hired Murphy to kill Curtis.
We need to find out who.
The old lady, the fucking shopkeeper,
someone knows where he is.
We're just gonna have to pry it from her.
Better find the loo.
Maybe the two of you can come up
with just one fucking idea while I'm gone.
Fimba!
What's that? My biggest fan.
She's stuck around.
What do you think?
It all looks so blood-testy.
I don't know who to root for.
Hey, Snaya.
What about you,
Fimba? Not too bad.
Be morea.
Look, she's around here somewhere.
Up to something, I'm sure.
She's grand.
We're good.
Good.
Okay, I'll see.
See you later tonight.
Hi.
Fimba, Murphy.
Dear and my cat.
It's Darren.
I've only seen her printed.
And they've printed a lot of a you, lady.
You tell me who ordered the hit,
or I'll put you down right
here to die in this shit-fed turf.
Look, we've killed each other's friends.
One for the other.
That's true, though.
I walk away.
I know.
No, no, no. Fuck you.
I killed a degenerate bottom feeder.
Curtis was my brother.
Then you must have
known about his tendencies.
Give me the name.
Easy.
All right.
I can bring him to you.
Easier that way.
And you're just going to have
this, whoever turned him's over.
Convinced your boy into a car, didn't I?
I'll be back here.
Yeah, it's back.
I'll be quiet.
No one else.
Oh, fuck right off.
Do you think I'm stupid?
We made it that pub.
Rights? That's it.
Full of merry fucking
villagers about that time.
None of who suspect you're a
murderer and bastard, I suppose.
So no tricks.
They won't have you hurting
anyone else in this time.
Do you hear me?
You'll be there.
Or we leave a special delivery
that'll blow that pub on over Donegal.
That happens to us.
People will come looking.
People are not worse than me.
And they'll tear right through
this guard for sake and place.
And that quaint little
nosy neighbor made yours.
No one will be safe.
Fuck it, Aegis.
Like a sound, you hear
that thing is in your ear.
But you can't forget from sundown songs.
It's all in the head,
you're ready everywhere.
No matter what you do, it's
gonna run around the whole door.
You take my pistol and nip off with a pit?
Certainly into your dramatic extension.
I find the leader.
She didn't take to my ceasefire.
She'll let me know it's yours.
I'm gonna finish her.
Finish all of them.
What's your plan on doing, Da?
It'll be good and public.
So if anyone comes looking
for blood, come for me.
Leave this time out of it.
You can go.
I'll be fine my own.
No way, Jose.
The great sin by Murphy's going to war.
I'll be fucked if we
miss never at all the fun.
Good boy.
Good dog.
Oh, yeah.
Can we gift for you?
Well, you take him.
He's yours.
What's his name?
You know, I never gave him a name.
What do you think?
He looks like a Sean.
Hi.
He'll take good care of him, won't he?
It's good to care.
Even if it hurts.
It keeps you human.
Okay.
Bye, Sean.
You want an audience?
I'll meet them inside.
Tell them I've got to fly it back.
Or I'll be waiting for them.
That's an advantage.
See?
I was listening.
No.
I have an advantage in my own.
Go on now.
Take this.
There's an envelope in the outer pocket.
Give it to Robert's mother for me.
The rest is yours.
What are you getting now?
We agreed with him.
We agreed on nothing.
Now listen.
There's nothing more here for you now.
This is my war.
Take that money.
Let it be my hand down to you.
You don't have to use that ever again.
You're young.
I need something else today.
Get the color from me.
I'm not saying you need to be
able to see it around like that.
It's just the wish there life doing this.
Nobody have a gaming unit.
My advice is more if I did than that money.
Trust me on this.
Go on.
Hi, Jesus.
Don't be denied that way.
Too expensive.
I've got no heart.
I have to be young.
Spread it.
Come on.
Sit down with you.
Black Star isn't a truth.
You didn't try adding out
the pitch? No, the crowd.
Right.
I have a peep in first Conan.
You've been the case in after.
I am.
Because you're shit with a pistol.
Because I went looking for
Curtis with no help from you.
Because I organized this trade.
And because I fucking said so.
Fine.
Just keep the car in these.
Annie found play you set that timer
and we get the fuck out of your ear.
Scorched a bastard.
So off of the licks, isn't it?
And someone can hang those
dead kids round our necks.
I'd hope for a quieter night.
I know a few stories, but it'll be yours.
Hey, you're getting on
with your own Russian book.
I've finished it yet.
I didn't say you would enjoy it, though.
Oh.
Been a mystery.
Been three, you know.
All right.
There's a clever detective
investigating the grace of murder.
Name of Porphyry is tenacious
in his quest with the truth.
Drawing out of this aspect, I'm
with his isolations destroying him.
Heading away at him.
I can't understand that the priority ended.
It's all right.
She came in stinks.
Nice detective.
It reminds me of you, actually.
Did you get his mind
in the end? I don't know.
Will your nephew be in tonight?
Or has he moved on?
You don't trade books for a living.
Do you feel, Mark?
What is it that you do?
Really?
You don't want to know.
If you need to tell me
something, I could help.
Jesus.
Why? Why? Come on.
You have to scoot on.
Where are you going?
This is no place for me.
Put him on the bar.
No, no.
Not tonight.
I just want Sean to be
in him, ah? Not tonight.
Take Sean and go home now.
But I... Sean can meet
your master mother tonight.
Okay? Go home.
No.
Why not? See you later.
Why is there a crowd?
Why?
Your partner's in crime.
He's had no funny business.
They're around to be sure of us.
They're just produced the fucker, like you
said, and you can get back to your music.
We'll meet out back where
we can hear ourselves.
You moved from that fucking
spot, and I promise you,
I'll shoot you dead.
All right, it was me.
Don't you love how a song can just
fill your hair with joy? Ha? The music.
Flicks you want to just
grab one of the nearest
young dolls and kiss
the face clean arper.
This how you can't score it.
And we're doing it.
Aren't I a bit ripe for your tongue?
Ah.
They'd care to get any
woman who's up for a...
Darren?
Rightful for your charity, Finn Bird.
But I think it's got to
be a singer first, only.
This him? And I'm done.
I told you.
It was me.
Course it's me.
Now, why don't we all
go out back and... Whoa!
No!
Don't!
It's mine, you bastard.
Don't bitch!
She shot me!
Just letting your own
shit in there, Darren!
No!
Why the fuck did you come back?
What's that? Stay down! Stay down!
Oh yeah, money's in me care.
Guessin' you're gonna have
to cut up a farm yet before me.
Finbar?
You lookin' for him to see of you.
I'm not the one who needs saving.
You've done what I've done.
I have no reasons.
And the Lord who's them.
I see no judgment from you.
I'm not here to judge.
We've all got our reasons.
Just shoot me.
You're at your hand.
Make your peace.
My brother.
He's all alone.
I'll make sure you join him.
His roots didn't get you.
Rita, I am so sorry.
It's fine, Finbar.
You never asked me what I did for a living.
Should I have? I see him.
Nothing grew.
I started it a days ago.
Whoa.
No, you keep it.
Maybe somewhere down
the road you'll try again.
Why, Rita?
You take care of him.